So if, you know, nearly half of all blacks are not okay with white people, according to this poll, not according to me, according to this poll, that's a hate group.
That's a hate group.
And I don't want to have anything to do with them.
And I would say, you know, based on the current way things are going, the best advice I would give to white people is to get the hell away from black people.
Just get the fuck away.
Wherever you have to go, just get away.
Because there's no fixing this.
This can't be fixed.
Right?
You just have to escape.
So that's what I did.
I went to a neighborhood where, you know, I have a very low black population.
Because unfortunately, you know, there's a high correlation between the density.
And this is according to Don Lemon, by the way.
So here I'm just quoting Don Lemon.
Okay.
When he notes that the, when he lived in a mostly black neighborhood, there were a bunch
of problems that he didn't see in white neighborhoods.
Is that right?
So even Don Lemon sees a big difference in your own quality of living.
Even Don Lemon.
Based on where you live and who's there.
So I think it makes no sense whatsoever as a white citizen of America to try to help black
citizens anymore.
Oh.
It doesn't make sense.
Because it's no longer a rational impulse.
Oh, because this is rational.
And so I'm going to, I'm going to back off from being helpful to black America because
it doesn't seem like it pays off.
Yeah.
Like I've been doing it all my life and I've been, the only outcome is I get called a racist.
Because you are.
That's the only outcome.
You're a racist.
It makes no sense to help black Americans if you're white.
It's over.
Don't, don't even think it's worth trying.
Totally not trying.
And you didn't expect that today, did you?
I want to focus on education.
You just need to get away from them.
Just get as much distance as you can.
That's my recommendation.
And I'm also really sick of seeing video after video of black Americans beating up non-black
citizens.
You mean white people who are racist?
You know, I realized it's anecdotal.
And it, you know, it doesn't give me a full picture of what's happening, but every damn
day I look on social media and there's some black person beating the shit out of some white
person.
I'm kind of over it.